cca.edu 2015-04-04

# Privacy Policy | California College of the Arts

This statement pertains exclusively to the collection of personal information on official California College of the Arts (CCA) websites. Official college websites use the domain name "cca.edu" and are controlled, operated, and maintained by college personnel in connection with college business. However, all uses of college computing resources are subject to the CCA Acceptable Use Policy.

## Collection of Personal Information

Generally, the college does not automatically collect the identity of individual users of or visitors to official college websites. If you are asked to provide personal information on an official college website, college policy provides that you should be notified of the following:

  * The purpose for which the personal information is collected
  * Any specific consequences for refusing to provide the information
  * Your right to inspect, amend, or correct personal records, if any
  * Whether the personal information is generally available for public inspection; and
  * Whether the personal information is made available or transferred to or shared with any entity

Unless otherwise notified by the collecting office, information provided to the college may be shared among offices within the college and outside entities as necessary or appropriate in the conduct of legitimate college business and consistent with applicable law. Individuals may inspect or correct, or both, their personal information as provided by the Public Records Act or applicable college policy.

The college is also subject to the disclosure requirements of the [Federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act](http://www2.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html).

Moreover, personal information you disclose to others via message boards and chat rooms may be collected and used by others who are not under the control of the college.

The college collects information that is available from server logs about user internet connections and visits to college websites. The college may use this information to analyze trends, create summary statistics for the purpose of determining technical design specifi- cations, and identify system performance or problem areas.

An example of information collected by servers include [Internet Protocol (IP) addresses](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IP_address) — a number assigned to your computer when you log on that is automatically identified when a computer connects to a server. (An IP address identifies the computer, not the computer user.)

College servers may log and track an IP address upon log-in and as the user moves from web page to web page within college websites. The college does not normally link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, so the identity of users remains anonymous to the college, but not, for example, the time users log on, log off, and how long they visit any one site.

The college uses IP addresses to identify a user when necessary to enforce compliance with law or college policies, for purposes of system administration, and to ascertain demographics and visitor usability.

Some college web pages may use ["cookies"](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) to better serve you with more tailored information when you return to the college site. (Cookies are identifiers a website can send to user browsers to keep on file in order to facilitate future visits to that site.) Users can set their browsers to receive notification when a website sends them a cookie so they may accept or reject it.

(Note: Some parts of a college web page that offers cookies may not function properly or may be considerably slower when users reject cookies.)

## Data Security

The college will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. The college strives to implement security measures that protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

Not all transmissions to and from official college websites are secure: the website may not encrypt or decrypt data sent to or from the website. In addition, email you send to a college address may be subject to interception. If your communication includes personal information you do not wish to provide electronically, contact the college by postal mail or telephone.

## Links to Other Sites

Some official college websites link to websites outside the "cca.edu" domain and are controlled and operated by third parties. The college is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites.

## Changes to Privacy Statement

Advances in technology, legal developments, and new college policies and practices may necessitate the need to change or update this privacy statement from time to time. The college reserves the right to change this policy without notice. It is the responsibility of the user to check this page for any changes to this policy.

## Questions or Concerns

Specific questions about the collection of personal information on specific official college websites should be addressed to the person identified on that site.

If you have comments or questions about this privacy statement or concerns about official college websites, please contact:

Educational Technology Services California College of the Arts 1111 Eighth Street, San Francisco CA 94107 Telephone: 800.447.1ART Email: [ets@cca.edu](mailto:ets@cca.edu)
